import 'package:math/models/question_model.dart';

List<QuestionModel> easy = [
  QuestionModel(
    level: "1",
    trueAnswer: "5",
    answerA: "4",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "3",
    questionText: "8 - 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "2",
    trueAnswer: "10",
    answerA: "11",
    answerB: "10",
    answerC: "20",
    answerD: "15",
    questionText: "2 x 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "3",
    trueAnswer: "3",
    answerA: "6",
    answerB: "4",
    answerC: "3",
    answerD: "5",
    questionText: "9 / 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "4",
    trueAnswer: "6",
    answerA: "4",
    answerB: "6",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "10",
    questionText: "4 + 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "5",
    trueAnswer: "15",
    answerA: "12",
    answerB: "8",
    answerC: "15",
    answerD: "16",
    questionText: "5 x 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "6",
    trueAnswer: "5",
    answerA: "6",
    answerB: "2",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "5",
    questionText: "10 / 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "7",
    trueAnswer: "3",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "4",
    answerD: "7",
    questionText: "6 - 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "8",
    trueAnswer: "11",
    answerA: "9",
    answerB: "7",
    answerC: "11",
    answerD: "8",
    questionText: "6 + 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "9",
    trueAnswer: "6",
    answerA: "5",
    answerB: "8",
    answerC: "4",
    answerD: "6",
    questionText: "2 x 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "10",
    trueAnswer: "4",
    answerA: "6",
    answerB: "4",
    answerC: "7",
    answerD: "2",
    questionText: "8 / 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "11",
    trueAnswer: "3",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "4",
    answerC: "1",
    answerD: "2",
    questionText: "5 - 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "12",
    trueAnswer: "7",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "7",
    questionText: "5 + 2",
  ),
];

List<QuestionModel> medium = [
  QuestionModel(
    level: "1",
    trueAnswer: "20",
    answerA: "12",
    answerB: "20",
    answerC: "15",
    answerD: "18",
    questionText: "4 x 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "2",
    trueAnswer: "3",
    answerA: "7",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "3",
    answerD: "12",
    questionText: "9 / 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "3",
    trueAnswer: "3",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "2",
    answerD: "1",
    questionText: "8 - 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "4",
    trueAnswer: "12",
    answerA: "10",
    answerB: "8",
    answerC: "14",
    answerD: "12",
    questionText: "7 + 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "5",
    trueAnswer: "32",
    answerA: "16",
    answerB: "30",
    answerC: "32",
    answerD: "25",
    questionText: "8 x 4",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "6",
    trueAnswer: "2",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "2",
    answerC: "4",
    answerD: "6",
    questionText: "8 / 4",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "7",
    trueAnswer: "4",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "2",
    answerD: "4",
    questionText: "7 - 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "8",
    trueAnswer: "3",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "2",
    answerD: "4",
    questionText: "6 / 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "9",
    trueAnswer: "25",
    answerA: "20",
    answerB: "25",
    answerC: "15",
    answerD: "10",
    questionText: "5 x 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "10",
    trueAnswer: "11",
    answerA: "9",
    answerB: "7",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "11",
    questionText: "7 + 4",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "11",
    trueAnswer: "2",
    answerA: "4",
    answerB: "6",
    answerC: "2",
    answerD: "3",
    questionText: "8 - 6",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "12",
    trueAnswer: "18",
    answerA: "18",
    answerB: "14",
    answerC: "16",
    answerD: "12",
    questionText: "6 x 3",
  ),
];

List<QuestionModel> hard = [
  QuestionModel(
    level: "1",
    trueAnswer: "6",
    answerA: "14",
    answerB: "6",
    answerC: "12",
    answerD: "17",
    questionText: "12 / 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "2",
    trueAnswer: "40",
    answerA: "35",
    answerB: "25",
    answerC: "45",
    answerD: "40",
    questionText: "5 x 8",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "3",
    trueAnswer: "19",
    answerA: "14",
    answerB: "19",
    answerC: "15",
    answerD: "13",
    questionText: "12 + 7",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "4",
    trueAnswer: "6",
    answerA: "8",
    answerB: "3",
    answerC: "5",
    answerD: "6",
    questionText: "9 - 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "5",
    trueAnswer: "39",
    answerA: "26",
    answerB: "37",
    answerC: "39",
    answerD: "33",
    questionText: "13 x 3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "6",
    trueAnswer: "4",
    answerA: "4",
    answerB: "6",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "2",
    questionText: "12  /  3",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "7",
    trueAnswer: "7",
    answerA: "5",
    answerB: "7",
    answerC: "3",
    answerD: "6",
    questionText: "9 - 2",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "8",
    trueAnswer: "16",
    answerA: "14",
    answerB: "12",
    answerC: "16",
    answerD: "13",
    questionText: "9 + 7",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "9",
    trueAnswer: "1",
    answerA: "3",
    answerB: "5",
    answerC: "0",
    answerD: "1",
    questionText: "11 / 11",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "10",
    trueAnswer: "20",
    answerA: "20",
    answerB: "25",
    answerC: "15",
    answerD: "18",
    questionText: "4 x 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "11",
    trueAnswer: "6",
    answerA: "5",
    answerB: "7",
    answerC: "8",
    answerD: "6",
    questionText: "11 - 5",
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    level: "12",
    trueAnswer: "15",
    answerA: "14",
    answerB: "11",
    answerC: "15",
    answerD: "13",
    questionText: "7 + 8",
  ),
];